when because you're so like determined
当因为你如此坚定
to
地决定每周上传两个视频并且你真的喜欢
really you've stuck with that you
你一直坚持你
haven't missed that
没有错过的
has there ever been times where you've
时候你曾经
like had to film
有过不得不拍摄的时候
and you've i don't know you've had like
，你已经 我不知道你是否度过
a stressful day or like you know you're
了紧张的一天，或者你知道你
really not feeling it and you just
真的没有感觉到它，
you're just like oh god i need to film
你就像天哪，我需要拍摄
and like you want to have that really
，就像你想要那本真正
positive or good bible
积极或好的圣经
or like your vibe and you're like you
或者喜欢你的氛围，你就像你
know what i
知道
just got to do it like if so how much
我要做的事情一样，如果发生了多少
does that happen
，
and like other than just
除了
just getting on with it is there any
只是继续它还有
other thing that you just feel like
其他任何事情，你只是觉得
you know are you good at like just
你知道你是你 擅长就像刚刚
getting through it
通过它
i love this question especially because
我喜欢这个问题，特别是因为
it was already this has this ever
它已经
potentially happened this happens i
发生了这种情况可能会发生这种情况我
think only in my last two three videos
认为只有在我的最后两个三个视频
have i actually felt so this is i was
中我才真正感受到所以这是我
yesterday in a one-to-one call and they
昨天在一个人中与某人交谈 - 一对一电话，
were like i just don't know i don't find
他们就像我只是不知道我觉得
this too much fun i'm like few videos
这不太有趣 我喜欢很少的视频，
okay what if i told you
好吧，如果我
in all honesty for so i have like 32 or
诚实地告诉你，那么
for my first 20 21 22 i was crying
我的第一个 20 21 22 有 32 或 33 个视频，我
before putting it out no before filming
在把它放出来之前哭了，没有在拍摄之前，然后在拍摄
it before putting it out
之后把它放出来
after filming filming it because i was
，因为 我
crying and i was texting anger saying
哭了，我愤怒地发短信说
i just put 20 hours of work into
我只是把 20 个小时的工作投入到
something it's so
某件事上，
like it's so bad anyone who's going
这太糟糕了，任何人
to watch this is going to think what is
看到这个都会想
this idiot doing
这个白痴在做什么
and i just cannot ever see the light of
，我就是永远看不到
day it's so obvious
曙光 它是如此明显
and so terrible and i hate it and i
，如此可怕，我讨厌它，我
hated it before doing it because i knew
在做之前讨厌它，因为我知道
i didn't have my script
我没有我的剧本，
i hated it after filming it because i
我在拍摄后讨厌它，因为
was like oh god
我就像天哪
that was so bad and i hated it after
，太糟糕了，我在编辑后讨厌
editing it because i wasted so much time
它 因为我浪费了很多时间
where i could be working or studying
在我可以工作或学习的地方
going into something terrible so this
做一些可怕的事情所以这
was my process
就是我的
every single video the only joy that i
每个视频的过程我唯一
got was when people would say oh this is
得到的快乐是人们会说哦这
actually okay and this is nice and the
实际上还可以，这很好，
videos would do well
视频也行 嗯，
the process itself was a show and a
这个过程本身就是一个 shi  t show
pain
痛苦
and the worst thing i have ever been
和我经历过的最糟糕的
through it was terrible
事情太
terrible did i ever want to film no i
可怕了我有没有想过拍摄不我
dreaded it i hated it i hated
害怕它我讨厌它我讨厌
the angle i had my old camera my old
这个角度我有我的旧相机我的旧
lens oh my god my old lens would destroy
镜头哦我的上帝我的旧镜头会 毁了
my face
我的脸，
so i would look weird and i was like i
所以我会看起来很奇怪，我就像我
hate this like
讨厌这样，因为
people will think that i look like this
人们会认为我看起来像这样，
because no one's commenting on it
因为没有人对此发表评论，
they're like oh my god
他们就像天哪，
so there was so much that went into me
所以我有很多
despising turning off my
鄙视关闭我的
turning on my camera but i think it was
打开我的相机，但我认为这
the bigger picture for me and that's
对我来说更像是一幅更大的画面，
when
就像三个视频一样，我会
strongly please don't say that you hate
强烈地说请不要说你讨厌
this yet because you do you absolutely
这个，因为你确实讨厌这个，
do
但很有可能 如果你
that that will change
那会改变
and um i will say
，嗯，我现在会说，
now like i look forward to filming
就像我期待
videos in a way um
以某种方式拍摄视频一样，
am i tired absolutely
我绝对累了
absolutely i've had over 100 hours of
我已经工作了 100 多个小时，
um for the last few weeks i'm exhausted
嗯，过去几周我已经筋疲力尽了，
i always film lasting at night so i'm
我总是在拍摄 持续到晚上，所以我
always putting out my camera at nine p.m
总是把我的相机放在 晚上
after 13 14 hours of um like doing
13 点 14 小时后的九点 就像整天做狗屎一样
and i'm dead my mom looks at my videos
，我死了我妈妈看着我的视频
and she's like i guess your eye bags
，她就像我猜你的眼袋
from here you don't look your eyes
从这里你不看你的
aren't shining and i'm like
眼睛不发光，我喜欢
where do you want this shine to come
你希望这种光芒从何
from i'm so
而来 我已经
dead you don't realize you should be
死了你没有意识到你应该
happy i'm even doing this
感到高兴 我什至在这样做
which is i don't take any excuses for
不要为自己找任何借口，
myself i'm like you're going to do this
我就像你会这样做
i don't care and working through that
我不在乎，
pain is my only
忍受那种痛苦是我唯一
like way of going through it and then i
喜欢的方式，然后我
hate myself enough so if i
很讨厌自己，所以如果
in the beginning i used to put it off
我一开始就用 推迟它
and i'd be like oh yeah i'll do this
，我会像哦，是的，我稍后会这样做，
or like i just don't feel i'm gonna
或者就像我只是不觉得我会
start feeling better that will never
开始感觉更好，这永远不会
happen
发生，
like i fully believe that for irrational
就像我完全相信，对于非理性的
feelings
感觉，
you will never get trained out of them
你永远不会得到训练 在他们中间，
you just need to ignore them and me
你只需要忽略他们，我
thinking that my face looks weird
认为我的脸看起来很奇怪
and that my videos are terrible and that
，我的视频很糟糕，互联网上的
everyone in the internet will hate me
每个人都知道 我会恨我
and i'm going to go in the news and i'm
，我要上新闻，我
going to be like the worst thing that
要成为有史以来发生的最糟糕的事情，
since like cern indented the internet
就像 Cern 缩进互联网一样
that's all irrational
，这一切都是不合理的
and it won't go away so it's up to me to
，它不会消失，所以这取决于我
like shut that off
喜欢 关闭它
and do the work as soon as possible and
并尽快完成工作，
you just get i think um better at it
我认为
put on large music when you're putting
当你在柔光箱上播放大型音乐时，你会更好地播放大型音乐，
like if you if you're lucky and unlucky
就像如果你幸运和不幸
and having to put a setup up
并且不得不进行设置一样
put on some loud music sing along to it
放一些响亮的音乐跟着它
and just like
唱歌就像
cry on the inside and do the video it's
在内心哭泣然后做视频这是
my tip
我的提示
people won't notice except your mom um
除了你妈妈之外人们不会注意到
so if i don't look tired that's great
所以如果我看起来不累那很好
because trust me i am
因为相信我我
okay awesome thank you for that i think
很好很棒 谢谢你，
i think i especially and maybe some
我想我特别想我，也许
other people need to hear that just like
其他一些人需要听到，就像
look you're always going to feel like
看起来你总是会觉得
you're never always going to want to do
你永远不会想要
it so just get it done
去做，所以就完成它
and you should be sponsored by nike or
，你应该 由耐克或
something because you just do it it
其他东西赞助，因为你只是这样做，这
seems like your cat trades which is
看起来就像你的猫交易，这
great it's honestly it's just honestly
很棒，很不错
yeah thank you for that
老实说是的，谢谢你